diodes.com 2019-05-12

# Website Privacy Policy | Diodes Incorporated

###### Website Privacy Policy

###### 1\. Scope and Content

This Privacy Policy explains how Diodes Incorporated, 4949 Hedgcoxe Road, Suite 200, Plano, Texas 75024 USA ("Diodes") handles your personal data collected through Diodes' website. Personal data is any information relating to an identified or identifiable person, for example, your e-mail address, name or phone number.

###### 2\. Anonymous Usage of Diodes' Website

You are welcome to visit Diodes' website while remaining anonymous and not revealing any personal data. Sharing your personal data is voluntary. However, if you choose not to provide certain information, you may not be able to take advantage of some of Diodes' website’s features and programs such as sales support, technical support, and download secure files that are not available to anonymous users. The information you provide to Diodes will better enable Diodes serve you better and to communicate with you regarding our products and your product needs.

###### 3\. Data We Collect and How We Use it

Diodes collects the personal data you enter into forms on the website, for example, your e-mail address, name, title, phone number, company name, city, state, and country that you enter when you submit a request using website forms. This personal data is same as your business card information. This data will be used to serve your request, for example, to provide you with the product and service information you asked for. Diodes also uses personal data to enhance the service of Diodes' website and to personalize information provided to you online or offline.

Your personal data is collected through, stored and processed by Diodes or service providers of Diodes.

In addition to personal data, Diodes collects certain information related to your website usage, including pages viewed, files downloaded, and forms filled to serve you better in a timely manner. We do send your enquiry request and personal data via an email to our employees and partners who could provide information requested via your enquiry.  We may also ask for your intentional use of our products, market segment, and application when you complete a specific form such as technical support, product samples, or technical collateral. Diodes collects the number of visitors to our websites, browsing patterns and areas of interest. We analyze this data to assess trends, statistics and customers' needs, to help us improve our websites, products and better serve our customers. We do not sell or share your personal data to third parties except our service providers and business partners, such as distributors, who help us serve our customers better.

###### 4\. Disclosure to Other Companies

Under certain circumstances, personal data may be given to Diodes' business partners when we believe your business interests will be served. For instance, if we need to ship products to you or to provide technical/sales support via our business partners like distributors or sales representatives, we will share your name and address with a carrier or business partner. Diodes will also release personal data if compelled by law to do so.

###### 5\. Access to your Personal Information

Our web site allows you to set up a personal account to interact with the company so you don’t have to enter the same information each time you interact with us via the website and you can keep your information up to date. You may access your [personal account](https://www.diodes.com/Security/login) to change your personal information.

###### 6\. Cookies

Cookies are small text files that our websites ask to place on your computer's hard drive. If your browser is set to accept cookies, then your browser adds the text in a small file. We do not use cookies to read any other information on your computer's hard drive. We use cookie technology to authenticate your access to various areas of our website, tailor its content to your preferences, to help us analyze web traffic in general and to recognize your web browser to make it easier for you to complete forms, keep forms simpler, and to track your web usage as described in section 3. . Cookies may be used in interactions where you request something from Diodes Incorporated's Contact Us technical support. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies, or to warn you before a cookie is placed. If you choose not to accept cookies, you may have to manually input user IDs and passwords to receive certain data.

###### 7\. Data Security

We aim to protect your personal data. Diodes uses a variety of commercially available security technologies to protect your personal data, including secure servers, firewalls and encryption of financial data. We will only transfer your data within the Diodes Incorporated and to our business partners, especially to our distribution and sales partners, if this serves to fulfill contracts or your interests.

###### 8\. Children under the Age of 13

Diodes' website does not target and is not intended for children under the age of 13. Diodes' values the privacy needs of these children and encourages parents to be an active participant in their child's online activities and interests. Diodes' website does not target children and will not knowingly collect data from them. If we discover personal data from a child that has been provided through Diodes' website that is targeted to adults and older children, we will eliminate that data. We do not ask for users’ age and nor we target or communicate with our users based on their age.

###### 9\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this policy. While we do not intend to make changes to this policy very often, it is always a good idea to double check our most current policy statement when you visit us to be sure that you have read and agree with what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it.

###### 10\. Diodes' Contact

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, you can click here at [Corporate Legal](mailto:Zech_Feng@diodes.com?subject=Corporate%20Legal "Corporate Legal email") to send an email request.

For any other web related issues please [contact us](https://go.pardot.com/l/27642/2016-10-18/9yy81h)

Policy last revised on May 19, 2018
